Guide to the Men's Basketball Game Film Collection, 1947-1996 UA.13.01.0005
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Men's Basketball Game Films
  - Maryland, 1996 January 28
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 5, 1996 January 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 159, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3425)
  - North Carolina, 1996 January 31
    Duke loss; score: 72-73
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1996 January 31; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 159, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3426)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 2, 1996 January 31; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 159, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3427)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 3, 1996 January 31; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 159, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3428)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 4, 1996 January 31; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 159, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3429)
  - Clemson, 1996 February 03
    Duke win; score: 83-53
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 1, 1996 February 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 159, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3430)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 2, 1996 February 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 159, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3431)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 3, 1996 February 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 159, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3432)
  - Georgia Tech, 1996 February 07
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 1, 1996 February 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 159, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3433)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 2, 1996 February 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 159, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3434)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 3, 1996 February 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 159, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3435)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Reel 4, 1996 February 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 159, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3436)
  - Wake Forest, 1996 February 11
    Duke loss; score: 65-79
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 1, 1996 February 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 159, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3437)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 2, 1996 February 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 159, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3438)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 3, 1996 February 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 160, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3439)
  - Virginia, 1996 February 14
    Duke win; score: 79-60
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 1, 1996 February 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 160, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3440)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 2, 1996 February 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 160, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3441)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 3, 1996 February 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 160, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3442)
  - NC State, 1996 February 17
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 1, 1996 February 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 160, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3443)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 2, 1996 February 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 160, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3444)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 3, 1996 February 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 160, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3445)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 4, 1996 February 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 160, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3446)
  - Florida State, 1996 February 22
    Duke win; score: 83-87
    - Duke vs. Florida State: Reel 1, 1996 February 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 160, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3447)
    - Duke vs. Florida State: Reel 2, 1996 February 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 160, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3448)
    - Duke vs. Florida State: Reel 3, 1996 February 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 160, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3449)
  - UCLA, 1996 February 25
    - Duke vs. UCLA: Reel 1, 1996 February 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 160, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3450)
    - Duke vs. UCLA: Reel 2, 1996 February 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 160, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3451)
    - Duke vs. UCLA: Reel 3, 1996 February 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 160, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3452)
  - Maryland, 1996 February 28
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 1, 1996 February 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 160, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3453)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 2, 1996 February 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 160, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3454)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 3, 1996 February 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 160, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3455)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 4, 1996 February 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 160, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3456)
  - North Carolina, 1996 March 03
    Duke loss; score: 78-84
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1996 March 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 161, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3457)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 2, 1996 March 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 161, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3458)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 3, 1996 March 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 161, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3459)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 4, 1996 March 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 161, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3460)
  - Maryland, 1996 March 08
    Duke loss; score: 69-82; ACC Tournament, Greensboro, NC
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 1, 1996 March 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 161, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3461)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 2, 1996 March 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 161, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3462)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 3, 1996 March 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 161, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3463)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 4, 1996 March 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 161, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-3464)
- Unprocessed game films, undated
  Small amount of unidentified films and use copies of original films.
  - UNC vs. Wake Forest: Reel 1, Early 1960s (Box 166, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0093)
    Filmed from television.